SAM: We're going to stall, Owais. We need to level out.
OWAIS: Hold on to your seat, Sam. We're going to make this plane fly.
L: What's going on? Why are we shaking so much?
ARAESA: Everyone, please fasten your seatbelts. We're experiencing some turbulence.
OWAIS: We're coming out of the dive. Hold on to your seats.
L: This is crazy! What's happening?
ARAESA: Everyone, please remain calm. This is just turbulence.
OWAIS: We're going to make it through this. Just hold on.
SAM: Owais, I think we're crashing. We need to do something.
ARAESA: Everyone, please stay calm. We're experiencing a minor storm.
L: This is insane! We're going to die!
OWAIS: We're not going to crash. We're going to make it through this.
SAM: What... what just happened?
OWAIS: We made it through the storm. We're going to land safely.
ARAESA: Everyone, please prepare for landing. We're starting our descent.
L: I... I think I'm going to be sick.