HAIDER: We can take him down, Iqra. I've been watching Hadi's racing schedule, we know exactly when and where he'll be.
IQRASH: But are we sure he's the one we want? What if he's not as weak as he seems?
HAIDER: He's our only chance at redemption, Iqra. We can't let him get away.
HAMMAD: Hey, guys, I couldn't help but overhear. Why don't we settle this like men, in the upcoming annual car race?
HAIDER: You think you're funny, don't you, Hammad? Trying to turn this into some joke.
HAMMAD: Not at all, my friend. I just think it's time we put our skills to the test.
HADI: Come on, baby, just a little more power...
HADI: I can do this. I have to do this.
HAIDER: Let's show him what we're made of, Iqra!
IQRASH: You got this, Haider. We're in this together.
HAIDER: What the...? How did he do that?
HAIDER: Congratulations, Hadi. You won this time.
HADI: Thanks, Haider. But it's not over yet.