ERIKA VALENTINA: Jason, I'm telling you, this is the breakthrough we've been waiting for.
JASON RYDER: I know, Erika, but we need to run more tests. We can't send a human through time without being absolutely sure.
ERIKA VALENTINA: We've run countless simulations. The technology is sound.
LUCIA FIORENTINA: Leo, I've been thinking... maybe it's time we took a closer look at this temporal anomaly.
LEO: What do you mean? We're not going to mess with the timeline again, are we?
LUCIA FIORENTINA: No, no, nothing like that. I just want to understand what's happening. It could be a game-changer for our research.
ERIKA VALENTINA: Alright, Jason, the time is now. Are you ready?
JASON RYDER: I'm as ready as I'll ever be.
LUCIA FIORENTINA: Wait, Erika, I don't think this is a good idea. We're not prepared for the consequences.
ERIKA VALENTINA: It's too late now, Lucia. The clock is ticking.