JAXON: Another dead body, another case gone cold.
LUNA: Jaxon, I think we have a lead on the latest victim.
JAXON: What kind of lead?
LUNA: A cryptic message on the comms system. It reads: 'Eclipse is coming.
JAXON: Sounds like a bunch of hype to me. Eclipse is just a myth.
KIARA: I didn't mean to see it. I didn't mean to hear it.
VICTOR: You're the one who's been snooping around, Kiara. I should've known.
LUNA: Jaxon, I think we're looking at a bigger picture here. This Eclipse thing is more than just a myth.
JAXON: What are you talking about?
LUNA: I think it's a warning. A warning that something big is coming, something that could change the course of the city's history.
JAXON: And you think this message on the comms system is the key to it all?