MAX: I need you to look into the disappearance of Kaida, a high-ranking exec at Omicron Innovations.
LUNA: What makes you think she's involved in something shady?
MAX: A cryptic message from her comms device hinted at a corporate conspiracy. I need someone with your... particular skills to help me dig deeper.
LUNA: What kind of skills?
MAX: According to the rumors, Kaida uncovered something about Omicron's latest project - codenamed 'Eclipse'. I'm guessing it's more than just a fancy new AI.
LUNA: You think it's connected to her disappearance?
VORON: What brings you two to our humble abode?
LUNA: Just passing through, enjoying the... ambiance.
LUNA: This is it. The Eclipse project - it's not just AI, it's a neural network that can predict and manipulate human behavior.
MAX: This changes everything. We need to get this info to the right people - people who can take down Omicron.
LUNA: And what about Kaida? Do we even know if she's still alive?