HAIDER: Alright, Iqrash, we got this. Hadi's been quiet lately, he's due for a hit.
IQRASH: I don't know, man. Hadi's not one to back down from a fight.
HAIDER: Don't worry, I've got a plan. We'll take him down, and then we'll be the top dogs in this city.
IQRASH: What's the plan, again?
HAIDER: We'll set up an ambush, and then we'll take him out. Easy as that.
HAMMAD: Hey, guys, why don't you settle this like civilized people? In the annual car race, of course.
HADI: Alright, baby, you're going to need to bring your A-game if we're going to take down Haider and Iqrash.
HADI: This engine's been tweaked to perfection. I can feel it in my bones, we're going to win this thing.
HAIDER: You think you can take me down, Hadi? I've been waiting for this moment for years.
HADI: I'm not just looking to take you down, Haider. I'm looking to crush you.
HADI: Come on, Haider! You can't keep up with me!
HAIDER: I'm not going down without a fight!
HAIDER: I...I didn't think you had it in you, Hadi.
HADI: You shouldn't have underestimated me, Haider. I'm the best driver in this city.