DR. THOMPSON: How's our patient doing today, Sofia?
NURSE VALENCIA: Stable, doctor. The patient's vitals are looking good.
DR. THOMPSON: Excellent. Let's take a look at the scans and see how the injury is healing.
JAXON REED: What...what happened?
NURSE VALENCIA: You were in an accident, Jaxon. You're safe now.
JAXON REED: An accident? I don't remember anything.
DR. THOMPSON: Don't worry, Jaxon. You've been through a lot. We'll get you back on your feet in no time.
JAXON REED: I had a dream...I was driving, and then...and then something happened.
NURSE VALENCIA: Try to relax, Jaxon. You're safe here.
DR. THOMPSON: We'll do some more tests in the morning, and we'll get to the bottom of this.
JAXON REED: I just want to go home...please.