HAIDER: We've been planning this for weeks, Iqrash. Hadi's got a reputation for being untouchable on the track.
IQRASH: We're not just going to take him down on the track, Haider. We're going to make it personal.
HADI OFFSCREEN: I'm not afraid of you two.
HAIDER: Oh, I think you should be.
HAMMAD: Wait, let's not do this. There's an annual car race coming up. Why don't we settle it there?
HAIDER: And put ourselves at the mercy of the judges? No way.
HADI: I've got the edge I need. Time to take these guys down.
HAMMAD: Good luck, Hadi. I'll be rooting for you.
ANNOUNCER VO: Welcome to the annual city car race! Your drivers include Hadi in the sleek blue car, Haider in the rugged red car, and many more!
HADI: I'm taking the lead!
HAIDER: No way! I'm not letting you win!
HADI: I did it!